Seitz, Peter Arbitration Files 5733
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- FMC Corp. vs USA Local 3828; Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corp vs. IAM Local 893; Falcon Carriers Inc. vs Marine Engineers Beneficial Association District 2, 1957-1979 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  Issue: Call in; Classification of jobs - duties performed, overlapping classifications; severance pay - technological displacement allowance. (Award Only.)
- Farmingdal Iron Works vs International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers Local 455, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  Withdrawn. RC, B, EX.
- Farrel-Birmingham Co. vs USA Local 3571; Federal Bearings Co. vs UAW Local 297; Fidesta Co. vs Retail Clerks Union Local 1357, 1957-1982 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - new classification; discipline - suspension, improper maintenance of records; contracting out - janitorial services; classification of jobs - upgrading; assignment of jobs - bargaining unit work. (Award Only).
- Forward Association, Inc. vs. American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  Withdrawn. AN, EX, SD, RC.
- Four Star Candy Co. vs. Warehouse and Processing Employees, Local 258, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  Issue: Welfare fund - employer's contribution.
- Fox Transport System Inc. vs. IBT, Local 500, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - plant rules. (Award only). RC, B, EX, AN, SD.
- Franklin General Hospital vs Nursing Home and Allied Health Services Union Local 144; French R.T., Co vs IBT Local 169; Friden, Inc. vs IUE Local 459, 1961- 1980 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  Issue: Rates of pay - shift differential; pension plan; discipline - suspension - leaving work area without permission; rates of pay - holidays, vacation; overtime distribution; rates of pay - merit increase; rates of pay - time not worked
- GAF Broadcasting Co., Inc. vs. AFTRA, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Issue: Rates of pay - classification of jobs. B, EX, AN, RC, SD. (No award).
- Garrett Buchanan Co. vs. Warehouse Employees, Local 169, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Issue: Absences; reinstatement. (Award only).
- Gearmotor and Transmission Components of the General Electric Co. vs. UAW, Local 191, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Issue: Layoff - temporary. (Award only).
- Geigy Chemical Corp. vs. ICW, Local 65, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Issue: Holidays and holiday pay - workweek. (Award only).
- General Bronze Corp. vs. Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers and Helpers International Union, Local 8, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- General Cable Corp vs MESA, Local 14; vs. IAM District Lodge 157; vs. IBEW, Local 1558, 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Issue: Vacation pay - layoff; recall - failure to recall; classification of jobs - combination of classifications; vacation pay - eligibility; seniority - transfer. (Award Only.)
- General Dynamics Corp., Electric Boat Division vs. Metal Trades Council of New London County, AFL-CIO, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Issue: Classification of jobs; Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages - union representatives; arbitrability - timeliness; arbitrability - contract interpretation. (Award Only.)
- General Dynamics Corp., Electric Boat Division vs Metal Trades Council of New London County, AFL-CIO; vs. IAM Lodge 1871, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Issue: Discipline - negligence and carelessness, suspension, discharge, absences. (Award Only.)
- General Dynamics Corp., Quincy Shipyard Division vs. Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Local 5; Electric Boat Division vs. Metal Trades Council of New London County, AFL-CIO; vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters, Local 1302, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; contracting out - bargaining unit work. (Award Only.)
- General Dynamics Corp., Electric Boat Division vs United Brotherhood of Carpenters, Local 1302; vs. Marine Draftmen's Association; vs. Boilermakers' Union Local 614; vs. Painters Local 1503; vs. IBEW Local 261, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension, discharge.
- General Electric Co. vs IUE Local 201, Local 225, Local 301, Local 283, Local 119, 1960-1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Issue: Arbitrability - jurisdiction; demotions - discipline; theft - company property; rates of pay - temporary job; evidence - admissibility; absences - sufficient reasons; evidence - admissibility; discipline - discharge; alcoholism, drinking and intoxi
- General Electric Co. vs IUE Local 201, Local 371, Local 203; vs. UAW, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Issue: Discipline - violation of plant rules, discharge.
- General Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 320, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Settled. RC. (No award).
- General Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 161, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - qualifications. RC, TR, B, EX, AN, SD.
- General Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 161. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Issue: Promotions - seniority. RC, TR, EX, B. (No award).
- General Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 255, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 15a)
- General Electric Co. vs. UE, Local 1202, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 15b)
  Settled. B, RC.
- General Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 761, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge. RC, B, EX, AN, SD. (No award).
- General Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 201, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- General Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 734, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  RC. (No award).
- General Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 371, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Issue: Transfers - seniority. EX, SD, TR, RC, B, AN.
- General Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 320, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  RC. Withdrawn.
- General Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 119, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Issue: Bumping - seniority. B, RC, TR, EX, AN.
- Getty Refining and Marking Co. vs OCAW; Gimbel Brothers vs RWDSU District 65; Globe Newspaper Co. vs Graphic Arts International Local 300, 1959- 1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Issue: Rates of pay - classification of jobs; discipline - discharge, suspension, insubordination.
- Grand Union Co. vs IBT, Local 456; Granite City Steel vs ICW Local 50; Gray James vs RWDSU District 65, 1957-1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Issue: Rates of pay - premium pay, reporting pay, holiday pay, strike or lockout. (Award Only.)
- Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. vs Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Local 484; vs. Amalgamated Meat cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 342, 1958-1960 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Issue: Arbitrability - grievance procedure, failure to follow; jurisdiction; arbitration procedures - appointment of arbitrators; rates of pay - reporting pay; plant rules - overtime; discipline - discharge, theft. (Award Only.)
- Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. vs IBT Local 852, Local 202; vs. Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union Local 484, Local 68, 1961-1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper personal conduct, plant rules, theft, company property; rates of pay - premium pay, scheduling; retirement - fringe benefits. (Award Only.)
- Greenwald Industries, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 810, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - plant rules - insubordination. (Award only).
- Grefco, Inc. vs. United Brick and Clay Workers of America, Eastern District 12, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination. RC, AN, EX, B. (No award).
- Greyhound Lines, Savannah, Georgia vs. ATU, Division 1493, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension - disloyalty. RC, AN, TR, B, SP.
- Greyhound Lines, Tulsa vs. ATU, Local 1313, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Greyhound Lines, Phoenix vs. ATU, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Issue: Contracting out - janitorial work. TR, RC, B, EX, AN, LD.
- Greyhound - Phoenix vs. ATU, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Issue: Vacations - schedules - vacation pay. RC, TR, SD, B, EX, AN.
- Greyhound Lines, Inc., Minneapolis vs. ATU, Local 1150, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - carelessness and negligence. RC, B, SD, AN, EX.
- Greyhound Lines, Inc., Los Angeles vs. ATU, Local 1222, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - falsifying records. TR, RC, B, EX. (No award).
- Greyhound Lines, Milwaukee vs. ATU, Local 1350, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences - reasons - false. RC, EX, B, SD, TR.
- Greyhound Lines, Milwaukee vs. ATU, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - change in procedure - past practice. TR, RC, B, EX, SD. (No award).
- Greyhound Lines, Milwaukee vs. ATU, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Greyhound Lines, Philadelphia vs. ATU, Local 1210, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - disloyalty. TR, RC, B, SD, EX. (No award).
- Greyhound Lines, Philadelphia vs. ATU, Local 1210, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Greyhound Lines, St. Louis vs. ATU, Local 1313, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Greyhound Lines, New York vs. ATU, Local 1202, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences - carelessness and negligence. RC, B, TR, EX, SD.
- Greyhound Lines, New York vs. ATU, Local 1202, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Greyhound Lines, Miami vs. ATU, Local 1326, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- ITT Continental Baking Co., Inc. vs. IBT, Local 550, Bakery Drivers Union, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- ITT Grinnell Corp. vs. International Molders and Allied Workers, Local 376, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Issue: Rates of pay - change of operation. (Award only).
- ITT Laboratories vs. IUE, Local 400, Professional and Salaried Division, 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Issue: Arbitrability - timeliness; bargaining units - supervisors and foremen, performance of unit work; layoff vacation pay; severance pay. (Award only).
- Iberia Air Lines of Spain vs. IAM, District 100, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Issue: Theft. (Award only).
- Independent Lock Co. vs. IUE, Local 290, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Issue: Arbitrability - contract silence; fringe benefits - bonuses. (Award only).
- Ingraham Co. vs. IUE, Local 260, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Issue: Arbitrability - contract interpretation; contracting out. (Award only).
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 4389, Local 1010, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Issue: Rates of pay - incentive plan; seniority - bidding; incentive pay and incentive systems; discipline - suspension; change in operations; promotions - seniority; inaccurate list; assignment of jobs - seniority; vacancies - temporary, posting; past pr
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1010, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Issue: Promotions - promotional sequence; incentive pay and incentive systems; bidding - failure to bid; discipline - negligence and carelessness; demotions - seniority; schedules of work - seniority; insubordination - refusal of work assignment; vacancie
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1010, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Issue: Vacancies - seniority; schedules of work - management rights; discipline - negligence and carelessness; seniority - computation; discipline - unsatisfactory work; reporting pay - lack of work; insubordination - refusal of work assignment - discipli
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1010, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - job descriptions; incentive pay and incentive systems - new machinery, change in operations; classification of jobs - new job; rates of pay - weekends and holiday work. (Award Only.)
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1010, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Issue: Incentive pay and incentive systems - management rights; discipline - negligence and carelessness; overtime - schedules of work; classification of jobs - evaluation of job factors; discipline - unsatisfactory work. (Award Only.)
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1010, Local 2179, Local 2099, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Issue: Layoff - lack of work; schedules of work - change of schedule; rates of pay - transfers; classification of jobs - new machinery; classification of jobs - added duties; discipline - discharge; absences - excessive. (Award Only.)
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1010, Local 2099, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Issue: Discipline - substandard performance; classification of jobs - upgrading; assignment of jobs- assignment outside work area; overtime - schedules of work; promotions - ability vs. seniority; discipline - unsatisfactory work; assignment of jobs - ass
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1010, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - assignment to work outside classification; promotions - seniority; insubordination - refusal of work assignment; overtime - schedules of work; rates of pay; classification of jobs - evaluation of job factors. (Award Only.)
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1010, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - change in work assignments; assignment of jobs - temporary; classification of jobs - discontinuance of classification or job; vacancies - temporary; vacancies - method of filling. (Award Only.)
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1010, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  Issue: Grievance and grievance procedure - filing requirements; discipline - violation of plant rules; discipline - substandard performance; incentive pay and incentive systems; schedules of work - overtime; incentive pay and incentive systems - new machi
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1010, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  Issue: Schedules of work - overtime; incentive pay and incentive systems; classification of jobs; vacancies - seniority; rates of pay - time not worked; physical disability - reinstatement following; schedules of work - assignment of jobs; schedules of wo
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1010, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  Issue: Overtime - schedules of work; rates of pay; incentive pay and incentive systems; absences - discipline, notice in general; crew size.
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1010, Local 2099, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  Issue: Schedules of work - seniority; vacancies - seniority; incentive pay and incentive systems; schedules of work - work day; assignment of jobs - overlapping classifications; demotions - health and disability; overtime - schedules of work; contract int
- Inland Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 1010; vs. USA, Great Lakes Seamen, Local 5000; vs. ICW, Local 659; vs. USA, Local 1422, 1959-1963 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  Issue: Crew size; assignment of jobs; insurance - employer contribution; holidays and holiday pay - birthday holiday; arbitrability - timeliness; holidays and holiday pay; past practice - rates of pay. (Award Only.)
- Internal Revenue Service vs. National Association of Internal Revenue Employees, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  Issue: Definitions - official. (Award only).
- International Association of Fire Fighters vs. International Union of Firefighters Staff Union, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  Issue: Termination of employment - retirement. B, EX, AN, RC. (No award).
- International Metal Specialties, Inc. vs. International Association of Bridge Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Shopmen's Local Union 455, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  Issue: Vacation pay. B, RC, AN, EX. (No award).
- International Silver Co. vs. USA, Local 7770, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  Issue: Rates of pay - piecework vs. day work. (Award only).
- International Smelting and Refining Co. vs. USA, Local 4985, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  Issue: Holidays and holiday pay - birthday holiday. (Award only).
- International Telephone and Telegraph Federal Division vs. IUE, Local 447, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  Issue: Rates of pay - combined job. (Award only).
- Iroquois Gas Corp. vs. IBEW, Local 2154, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - remedy for improper assignment. (Award only).
- Jamaica Water Supply Co. vs. Utility Workers Union of America, Local 374, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  Issue: Sick leave and sick pay. (Award only).
- Jersey Central Power and Light Co. vs. IBEW, Local 1309, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- John Bath and Co., Inc. vs. USA, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  Issue: Arbitrability - timeliness. (Award only).
- John Engelhorn and Sons vs. United Packinghouse, Food and Allied Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 49-A, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Co. vs Insurance Workers International Union (IWIU), 1960-1977 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  Issue: Reinstatement - following illness or physical disability; fringe benefits - disability benefits; rates of pay - change in product; termination of employment - elimination of jobs; discipline - unsatisfactory work. (Award Only.)
- Johns-Manville Products Corp. vs. GBBA, Local 145, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; absences - excessive. (Award only).
- Joseph Schlitz Brewing Co. vs. IBT, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  Issue: Management rights - change of job duties. (Award only).
- KLM Royal Dutch Airlines vs. TWU, Air Transport Local 504, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Karagheusian, A and M, Inc. vs. Textile Workers Union of America, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  Issue: Rates of pay - increase. (Award only).
- Kelsey-Hayes Co., Heintz Division vs. UAW, Local 834, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Kennecott Refining Corp. vs. USA, Local 5977, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  Issue: Reporting pay; shift scheduling - double shift. TR, EX, SD.
- Keystone Lighting Corp. vs. IBEW, Local 1814, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  Issue: Arbitrability - timeliness; absences - notice. (Award only).
- Kidde, Walter and Co. vs. UAW, Local 436, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Kidde Manufacturing Co. vs IUE Local 472, Local 462, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension; rates of pay - increase; holidays and holiday pay - workweek. (Award Only).
- Kingsbrook Jewish Medical Center vs. Drug and Hospital Union, Local 1199, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  Issue: Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages - work stoppages. (Award only).
- Kings Highway Hospital Center, Inc. vs. RWDSU, the Registered Nurses Division of District 1199, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  Issue: Rates of pay - past practice. (Award only).
- Knights of Columbus, National Headquarters vs OPEIU, Local 329, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - upgrading; promotions - seniority. (Award Only.)
- Kollmorgen Optical Corp. vs IAM, Pioneer Valley Lodge, Local 2175, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  Issue: Union representatives and business - time off for union business. (Award Only).
- Kollsman Instrument Corp. vs IAM, District 15, 1958-1961 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  Issue: Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages - vacation pay computation; contracting out - layoff. (Award Only.)
- Kraft Foods vs IBT Local 277; UAW Local 1881, 1963-1977 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  Issue: Shutdown - economic reasons; strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages - strike misconduct. (Award Only.)
- La Prensa vs. ANG, Newspaper Guild of New York, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  Issue: Arbitrability - membership in bargaining unit. (Award only).
- League of New York Theaters, Inc. vs. Actors' Equity Association, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  Issue: Rates of pay - time not worked. (Award only).
- Lee Letter Service vs. Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Local 1, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Legal Aid Society vs Association of Legal Aid Attorneys, 1978-1978 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  Issue: Arbitrability - probationary employee.
- Lederle Laboratories, Inc. vs. ICW, Local 143, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - overtime. AN, B, EX, A.
- Lehigh Portland Cement Co. vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union (CLGW), Local 8, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  Issue: Arbitrability - jurisdiction; fringe benefits - supplemental unemployment benefits. (Award only).
- Leno, George Associates, Inc. vs. Warehousemen Employees, Local Union 169, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension; absences - excessive. (Award only).
- Lenox Hill Hospital vs Doris Turner; vs. RWDSU, Drug and Hospital Union, Local 1199, 1960-1974 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  Issue: Insubordination - discipline; classification of jobs - rates of pay. (Award Only.)
- Leschel Buick-Opel, Inc. vs UAW, Local 259, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  Issue: Contracting out - layoff. (Award Only.)
- Lever Brothers Co. vs ICW, Local 51, 1961-1978 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  Issue: Discipline - violation of plant rules; management rights - contracting out. (Award Only.)
- Linde Co. vs Hourly Employees of Neward Oxweld Employees' Association, Inc., 1961 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  Issue: Classification of jobs; assignment of jobs - seniority. (Award Only.)
- Lindenhurst Union Free School District, Board of Education vs Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Lindenhurst Unit, Suffolk Educational Chapter, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  Issue: Rates of pay - increase. (Award Only.)
- Liquidometer Corp. vs. IUE, Local 452, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  Issue: Absences - excessive; absences - discipline. (Award only).
- Lockheed Aircraft Service Co. vs. IAM, Local 1834, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - transfer of work. (Award only).
- Long Island Daily Press vs. New York Mailers Union Number 6, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Long Island Water Corp. vs. Utility Workers of America, Local 365, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  Issue: Seniority - vacation scheduling; vacations - scheduling. (Award only).
- Louisville Gas and Electric vs. IBEW, Local 2100, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Lux Clock Manufacturing Co., Inc. vs. UAW, Local 1251, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  Issue: Arbitration procedure - multiple grievances. (Award only).
- Lux Time Division, Robertshaw-Fulton Controls vs. UAW, Local 1251, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  Issue: Rates of pay - equal pay for equal work. (Award only).
- Lycoming Division, Avco Manufacturing Corp. vs. UAW, Local 1010, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  Issue: Promotions - seniority. (Award only).
- MacAndrews and Forbes Co. vs Licorice and Paper Employees Association; Mack Trucks, Inc. vs UAW, Local 259, 1958-1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Issue: Rates of pay - classification; schedules of work - weekend; discipline - discharge - improper job attitude. (Award Only.)
- Mack Trucks, Inc. vs UAW Local 229, 1954-1960 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - alcoholism; rates of pay - holiday pay; discipline - demotion. (Award Only.)
- Mack Trucks, Inc. vs UAW Local 229, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension - fights and altercations; rates of pay - overtime; rates of pay - holiday pay. (Award Only.)
- Macy. R.H. and Co. vs RWDSU, Local 1-5, 1957-1960 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension - improper job attitude; rates of pay - reclassification. (Award Only.)
- Madison Square Garden, Inc. vs SEIU Local 177; Mamaroneck Board of Education vs Mamaroneck Teachers Association, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge, rates of pay; discipline - discharge, probationary employee, leaves of absence, maternity leave. (Award Only.)
- Mamaroneck Board of Education vs Mamaroneck Teachers Association, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Settled. AN, RC, B, SD.
- Mamaroneck Board of Education vs Mamaroneck Teachers Association, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Issue: Retirement - incentive system - pension plan.
- Manhattan and Bronx Surface Transit Operating Authority vs Transit Supervisors Organization, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - misconduct. RC, AN, B, EX.
- Marlin-Rockwell, Inc vs UAW Local 197; McAllister Brothers, Inc. vs International Longshoremen's Association, 1977-1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - seniority - change of duties; assignment of jobs - change in location.
- McDaniel Ford, Inc. vs UAW Local 259, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Issue: Layoff - holiday pay. RC, B, AW, EX.
- McDowell Co., Inc. vs USA; McGraw Edison Co. vs IUE Local 467, 1958-1960 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Issue: Recall - seniority; seniority - disability, accident proneness. (Award Only.)
- McNichol Co. vs IBT Local 500; McPhee Ltd vs IBEW Local 35, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper personal conduct; fringe benefits, pension funds, welfare fund.